A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Declinations and Project Authorizations, 1934-2011; 2
  - Declinations - L-T, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 391, Folder 1-9)
  - Declinations - U-Z, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 392, Folder 1-5)
  - Declinations - A-D, 2010 July-2011 June (Box 392, Folder 6-9)
  - Declinations - E-O, 2010 July-2011 June (Box 393, Folder 1-11)
  - Declinations - P-Z, 2010 July-2011 June (Box 394, Folder 1-10)
  - Declinations - Individuals, 2009 July-August (Box 394, Folder 11)
  - Declinations - Individuals, 2009 September-2010 April (Box 395, Folder 1-4)
  - Declinations - Individuals, 2010 May-June (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - International, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 396, Folder 2-3)
  - Declinations - Businesses, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 396, Folder 4-5)
  - Declinations - Individuals, 2010 July-2011 April (Box 397, Folder 1-5)
  - Declinations - Individuals, 2011 May-June (Box 398, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - International, 2010 July-June 2011 (Box 398, Folder 2-3)
  - Declinations - Business, 2010 July-December (Box 398, Folder 4)
  - Declinations - Business, 2011 January-June (Box 399, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - Declined at November 2009 Board Proposal Review, 2009 November (Box 399, Folder 2)
  - Declinations - Declined at April 2010 Board Proposal Review, 2010 April (Box 399, Folder 3)
  - Declinations - Declined at November 2010 Board Proposal Review, 2010 November (Box 399, Folder 4)
  - Declinations - Declined at July 2010 Board Proposal Review, 2010 July (Box 400, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - Declined at April 2011 Board Proposal Review, 2011 April (Box 400, Folder 2)
  - Turn-Downs, 1934 June-1952 November (Box 407, Folder 3)
  - Turn-Downs, 1953-1973 (Box 408, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - A-B, 1998 August-2000 June (Box 409, Folder 1-5)
  - Turn-Downs - B-C, 1998 August-2000 June (Box 410, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - C, 1998 August-2000 June (Box 411, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - C-F, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 412, Folder 1-5)
  - Turn-Downs - G-H, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 413, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - H-J, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 414, Folder 1-5)
  - Turn-Downs - K-M, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 415, Folder 1-6)
  - Turn-Downs - M-N, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 416, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - N, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 417, Folder 1-5)
  - Turn-Downs - O-P, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 418, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - Q-, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 419, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - S, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 420, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - T-V, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 421, Folder 1-4)
  - Turn-Downs - W-Z, 1999 July-2000 June (Box 422, Folder 1-4)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1985-2003; 3
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
  Sound recordings; Moving Images
  - Treatment Choices for Benign Uterine Conditions: A Shared Decision-making Program Videotape, Foundation for Informed Medical Decision Making, Hanover, NH, 1995; 41 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11765)
    Access copy available.
  - Hormone Replacement Therapy, A Shared Decision-making Program Videotape, Foundation for Informed Medical Decision Making, Hanover, NH, 1995; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11766)
  - A Winning Proposition, Commonwealth Fund-Johns Hopkins Hospital Youth Mentoring Program, 1998 August 10; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11767)
  - DOT-NHTSA - Crashing Glasses, The Driver, Aretha Franklin "Think", Magic Johnson, 30 second Public Service Announcements, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11768)
  - Designated Driver - WBZ-TV, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11769)
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives: Composite Tape - Public Service Announcements and News Coverage, Harvard Center for Health Communication, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11770)
  - Vince and Larry, 16 Public Service Announcements, 1985-1988; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11771)
  - Mothers Against Driving Drunk (MADD) - Eight Public Service Announcements, 1988-1989; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11772)
  - Chicago Uninsured, Commonwealth Fund Global Strategy Group, 1999 February 16; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11773)
  - Insurance Reform, Commonwealth Focus Group, Chicago, 8PM, Insured - Global Strategy Group, 1999 February 16; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11774)
  - Miami, FL - Commonwealth Fund, Global Strategy Group, Health Care Reform: Uninsured - 6 pm, 1999 February 18; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11775)
  - Miami, FL - Commonwealth Fund, Global Strategy Group, Health Care Reform: Insured - 8pm, 1999 February 18; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11776)
  - Commonwealth II - 6pm, Uninsured Adults, Global Strategy Group, 1999 February 2; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11781)
  - Commonwealth II - 8pm, Insured Adults, Global Strategy Group, 1999 February 2; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11777)
  - Health Care Reform, Commonwealth Focus Groups, Global Strategy Group, 6PM, Los Angeles, 1999 February 11; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11780)
  - Los Angeles, CA - Health Care Reform, Commonwealth, Insured, 8pm, Global Strategy Group, 1999 February 11; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11778)
  - The Commonwealth Fund Development - Burlington, Vermont, 3:30pm, 2000 June 13; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11786)
  - The Commonwealth Fund Development - Burlington, Vermont, 6pm, 2000 June 13; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11787)
  - Low Income Mothers: Commonwealth Fund Development - 3pm, 2000 June 28; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11788)
  - Low Income Mothers: Commonwealth Fund Development - 6pm, 2000 June 28; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11789)
  - Residents Have the Answers: Improving Quality of Life in Long-term Care, 2001; VHS; 33 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11792)
  - On the Spectrum: Children and Autism, 2001; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11791)
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives: Public Service Announcements - 1. Red Light, 2. Kids, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11779)
  - Cooperative Caring Network (CCN) - People and Organizations Working Together to Help One Another, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11782)
  - Outward Bound, Diabetes Program, 8 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11783)
  - Everyone Wins: Quality Care Without Restraints, 1994 October 26; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11784)
  - Proudly Presents: Association of Maternal and Child Health Programs, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11790)
  - Designated Driver, Tony Schwartz - WRKO-ABC, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 9 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9986)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    There is a small period of silence between each "reminder"
    Barbara Wallace, Massachusetts Saving Lives Program lists "Reminders" about the importance of designated driving. Topics include statistics on drunk driving and alcohol-related car crashes.
  - How Information Technology Can Improve Healthcare Quality (World Congress Interpretation Systems, Inc.) - Tape 1, 2003 November 14; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 90 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9987)
    Introduction by Edward Howard, Alliance for Health Reform followed by a series of panels covering information technology (its benefits and barriers) and the role of government in information technology.
  - How Information Technology Can Improve Healthcare Quality (World Congress Interpretation Systems, Inc.) - Tape 2, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 89 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9988)
    Continuation of a series of panels covering information technology (its benefits and barriers) and the role of government in information technology.
  - Saving Lives Composite Public Service Announcements (5-90), Harvard Center for Health Communication, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 16 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9989)
    PSAs produced or acquired by the Harvard Center for Health Communication in support of the Massachusetts Saving Lives program.
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives Program - Two Public Service Announcements "Cindi", 1/4 inch audio cassette; 2 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9990)
    Public service announcements regarding the dangers of drunk driving and seatbelt safety.
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives - Two Public Service Announcements: 1. Cyndi, 2. Drink Driving, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 2 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9991)
    Public service announcements regarding the dangers of drunk driving and seatbelt safety. Duplicate of AV 9990.
  - Massachusetts Saving Lives Program - Public Service Announcement: Juan and Traci, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 1 minute (Box 1, Tape AV 9992)
    Public service announcement about seatbelt safety.
  - Northampton Saving Lives - Two Public Service Announcements, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 2 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 9993)
    Public service announcements about the dangers of speeding and seatbelt safety.